João Paulo Valadares

Rua José Godinho, 317 Cataguases, Minas Gerais, 36774-128

(32) 9 9835-0151

jotapvaladares@icloud.com

Resume

Graduated in Control and Automation Engineering from CEFET-MG (Federal Center for Technological Education of Minas Gerais) and certified by FGV (Getulio Vargas Foundation) and Rocketseat. I have 5 years of experience in the development field. I also worked as a statistics monitor at the Federal Center for Technological Education of Minas Gerais for 3 years and served as a Project Manager at "Rede Ciência Sem Fronteiras" (now known as "Em Rede").

I have experience with various programming languages, such as Javascript, Typescript, Python, Ruby, Java, PHP, and C#, as well as technologies and frameworks like React, Angular, Vue, Ember, Backbone, Preact, Django, Express, Spring, Ruby on Rails, Elixir, and Laravel.

During my time at the Federal Center for Technological Education, I served as a statistics monitor for 3 years and, at "Rede Ciências Sem Fronteiras," my main role was organizing foreign language learning projects, such as the Conversation Club and the English Class.

Experience

F2F / Full-Stack Developer

APRIL 2022 - JULY 2023, SÃO PAULO - SP

Energisa / Full-Stack Developer

OCTOBER 2021 - APRIL DE 2022, CATAGUASES - MG

Energisa / Database Analyst (Internship)

MARCH 2021 - OCTOBER 2021, CATAGUASES - MG

360Web / Full-Stack Developer

MARCH 2020 - MARCH 2021, LEOPOLDINA - MG

360Web / Front-End Developer

JANUARY 2019 - MARCH 2020, LEOPOLDINA - MG

Education

FGV / Data Science

NOVEMBER 2021, ONLINE

Rocketseat / Ignite (React, React Native, Node.js e Elixir)

JANUARY 2021 - JANUARY 2022, ONLINE

CEFET-MG / Control and Automation Engineering

MARCH 2016 - JANUARY 2022, LEOPOLDINA - MG

Additional activities

CEFET-MG / Statistics Monitor

JANUARY 2019 - JANUARY 2022, LEOPOLDINA - MG

Rede CSF / Project Manager

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2020, LEOPOLDINA - MG